yorkittran.github.io | LinkedIn | GitHub Email: yorkittran@gmail.com | Mobile: +84 366 08 2301

### Summary

I am interested in building and improving software systems. I'm now looking for opportunities to work in a high growth and challenging environment with a strong emphasis on engineering effort.

• 2 years of experience in developing application.

• Full stack web developer, with a focus on back-end systems and services.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : Ruby, JavaScript

Frameworks/Libraries : Ruby on Rails, Hotwire, NodeJS, VueJS, Express, NestJS

Databases : MySQL, MongoDB

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, Github

## EXPERIENCE

CodeLink HCMC

Full Stack Developer Oct 2022 – Feb 2023

CodeLink is a multinational development consultancy. We approach product development through design thinking methodologies and strategies to rapidly develop digital products and platforms following a disciplined agile process.

Baonoi NodeJS, Flutter, ReactJS, Python, Firebase, PostgreSQL

Baonoi is an audio news application that convert from many famous online news in Vietnam. Although still in beta phase, it has around 1000 users using everyday.

- \* I focused on APIs, transformed Firebase to PostgreSQL, and implemented some small features on mobile such as changing password, pulling to reload.
- \* Team size: 8

Raksul Vietnam HCMC

Backend Engineer Aug 2020 - Oct 2022

Raksul is a fabless B2B platform builder. We aims to change the world by reinventing legacy industry structures with the power of the Internet.

Novelty Ruby on Rails, VueJS, MySQL, GraphQL

Novelty is a successfully e-commerce application in Japan. We selling merchandises and allow user to put their own print into their buying product. We also support partner which is material supplier to keep track on the orders.

- \* I was responsible for the development and maintenance of many features, such as building files and send to partner for tracking orders, improving performance of requests, building 3D preview for the products, etc.
- \* Team size: 10

### Cutting cost with Lambda - Hackweek Edition

NodeJS, Ruby on Rails, AWS

Location: District 7, HCMC

Cutting cost with Lambda is a prototype that we made for reduce cost from Workers on ECs by transform to Lambda functions

- \* We built the prototype in 3 days that processing and previewing images through Lambda functions instead of Workers running on ECs. I transformed logic from back-end to Lambda functions, and handled to redirect to API Gateway.
- \* As calculation, we saved about 2000\$/month for the company if it successfully applied on other products. Therefore, we won the 1st prize of Effective Award in Hackweek competition with held once a year by Raksul Headquarter.
- \* Worked with many services on AWS: Lambda, API Gateway, SNS
- \* Team size: 3

Digital Product

NodeJS, MySQL, AWS

Digital Product is an application that allowed venue/ads owners to create QR codes and assign it to banner ads. Then it will be delivered to many different location and the owners can track the effectiveness of them.

- \* I built the prototype alone in 4 weeks using many AWS to create a serverless application. After 6 months of testing, it proved successfully and was integrated into a bigger product.
- \* Worked with many services on AWS: Lambda, RDS, S3, API Gateway, SAM
- \* Team size: 2

### **Advertised Marketing**

Ruby on Rails, VueJS, MySQL, GraphQL, Google APIs

Advertised Marketing is a project that allows user to create their orders of newspaper or advertised flyers, then support user to pick an area directly on the map to deliver them to customers via mailbox.

- \* I was responsible for developing operation part. This one help internal users in company to keep track on user orders. I focused on tracking order statuses, managing file that user upload, viewing comment of other internal users.
- \* Team size: 8

**PRO** 

Ruby on Rails, VueJS, Python, MySQL

PRO is a special e-commerce application. It mostly focuses on specific customers instead of normal users, which is a business partner companies. Customers will have a preferential price as large amount as the orders.

- \* I was responsible for the development and operation of the application. Beside implementing features on back-end, I also have a chance to learn VueJS by helping create components and pages on front-end side, such as price table, cart pages, etc. By using Python, we also create a crawler to make a comparison prices between competing company's products and ours.
- \* Team size: 4

## Act Brain Vietnam Corporation

HCMC

Backend Engineer Intern

Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

Act Brain is the consultants, provide solutions and develop leading software systems in Japan. We have a young and enthusiastic staff, with creativity and professional qualifications.

# **BPO Shinjin**

PHP, Zend Framework, MySQL

BPO Shinjin is an internal product for managing employees by tracking time sheet, build monthly quizzes.

- \* I built and maintained creating quizzes feature and covered test cases.
- \* Team size: 10+

### **EDUCATION**

FPT University

HCMC

Bachelor of Software Engineering with Scholarship

Sep 2017 - Jan 2021

## Le Quy Don Gifted High School

Information & Technology Specialized Class

Da Nang

Sep 2014 - May 2017

## PROJECTS

## Quizk

Ruby on Rails, VueJS, Hotwire, MySQL, DigitalOcean

Quizk is a quiz system for University of Medical and Pharmacy in HCMC to operates a internal competition.

- I was responsible for the development and operation of the application. After 2 months of developing, we success to run it in 3 weeks for serving about 3000 new students in university.
- I built the application using Ruby on Rails to create operation site and APIs, designed whole system included database and architecture. Also tried to deploy application to DigitalOcean
- Team size: 2